(Igawa) Mayumi... Which one are you?
Igawa is me though
Someone else is pretending to be me
no one remembers me
I don't understand...
what is happening
(Yuri) Please contact me if you have any questions.
Let's look for more people who remember Mr. Igawa.
Igawa-kun? Mayumi-san, how are you doing?
It wasn't a lie...
i love mayumi
let's go
Ah...
≪Two years ago, my husband, Yusuke Ninomiya, died≫
"(cry)"
≪A person just like her husband appeared≫
≪I thought my husband had come back to life≫
There's something I want you to see
It's my husband
Do you know which one?
≪I thought my husband had come back≫
≪Please, the three of us again...≫
Mayumi-san, how are you doing?
You also remembered Mayumi.
It wasn't a lie...
♬〜
≪Please...≫
(chime)
Welcome back
I'm home
Someone who looks like daddy?
I'm already home
Huh? Did you bring that back?
(Kento) Yeah tomorrow test?
(Sage) Yeah.
Did you want Mr. Igawa to listen to it?
(sage) no particular
Okay, mom should listen to it hahahaha
Choi choi choi choi (sage) hahahaha
♬〜
yeah? Are you planning to eat cucumber again?
Because I don't like or dislike things that I don't really like.
Daddy was also left behind.
I don't manage things like that.
yeah! Then please do what mommy does.
Hmm! delicious cucumber
It's shining, it's sparkling
I'll have it
yeah! delicious
Cucumbers were so sweet and delicious! It was amazing!
Well, I'll give it to you.
Cola! Please eat it yourself
♬〜
I thought you really came back.
《Did you sleep yet? 》
《Yeah, soundly》
(Ninomiya)《No, which one? 》
♬〜
《Hehe again? 》
《It smells good》
《I know》 《(sniffing sound)》
《Yes, the smell of the sun》 《Hehe》
《I wonder if it will come someday? " "yeah? 》
《The day when a wise man smells like an old man》
《Hehe what? that"
《Ah... I feel like crying when I think about it》
《Which one is that? Are they tears of joy at growing up?
Are they sad tears that smell like an old man from a wise man?
《6 4》 《It's quite competitive》
《Lie lie lie》
``I'm looking forward to the three of us drinking together.''
《You're quite quick.》
《Until then, we need to stay healthy》
《Yes》
♬〜
The three of us promised to drink together.
Yes (Sage) I'll go.
Yes, please be careful when you go.
♬〜
I'm coming (Mayumi) Welcome.
Ah, a snack for Peter, please.
Yeah (Mayumi) Hehe, please come.
yes
Ah... Mr. Igawa!
Sorry all of a sudden, I got a little worried...
Huh?
I'm glad you got home safely.
that…
Which one are you?
Huh?
Have we met somewhere?
♬〜
Ah... no, sorry if I forgot.
Haha...
Ah... Are you a member of Harunagien's family?
home…
Even if I ask your name...
This is Ninomiya, Mr. Ninomiya...
Eh... I'm sorry, I can't remember.
Ah... I'm sorry, please excuse me.
♬〜
(sigh)
Eh...
Ugh...
(sigh)
(engine sound)
Welcome back
I'm home now
Were you together? Oh, just there
(Sage) Yeah
Dinner, wait a minute, I'll make it right away.
Shall I help you? Are you okay
Kento Wash your hands and do your homework (Kento) Yes.
Shall I help you?
Are you okay
Even if I offer to help, I'm alone
Hehe, please change the water for the flowers.
yes
♬〜
(Osamu) Dad was extremely smart.
(Sage) From uncle?
Hmm, I guess I'll lose a bit to the old man, hehe.
What was your uncle's nickname when he was in high school?
It was fried rice.
Huh? any problem
I can figure it out quickly enough to make fried rice.
Hey hahahaha
Sorry, I could have called you.
(Osamu) It's okay, I wanted to see Kento's face too.
What happened with (Oji)? Talk?
Is it so easy for people's memories to disappear?
Huh? why? Did something happen?
no…
I met one of the parents at the cram school and said hello about a week ago.
Since then, we have seen each other from time to time.
I was surprised when you said "Nice to meet you" today.
Is there such a thing?
Oh, if I hit my head and lose my memory
I wonder if that could happen?
An accident? Yes, and besides that
This can happen when you suffer a mental shock.
I see...
When my mother died
That's why I don't remember much...
Ah... sorry
I didn't mean to say that.
No, it's okay
Well, to be honest, there's a lot we don't understand about the structure of the brain.
After decades of research, I am amazed every day.
(Sound of door opening) (Sage) Mom, I'm here.
Yes, I'm going
Thank you (Oji) Hey Kento, I'm here.
Excuse me (Tada), thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work (Tada) Please be careful when going home
♬〜
Looks like it's okay
It was quite fun, but I also had a life pretending to be Igawa-kun.
"Living with Mayumi Igawa", right?
I can't deny it, it's creepy
You don't have to say things that are obvious
Huh... hahaha
Hahahaha!
No way...
The look on your face when you found out Igawa was alive.
It's funny when I remember it
《Ah, Mukai-san》
《Sorry, I was in the hospital for a week after the accident》
《Are you meeting? " "yeah? 》
(Mukai)《If so, please accept the reception》
Because the security guard doesn't know anything, so I don't know what to do.
If there were no security guards
It all ended there.
Well, you just have to be ready.
If something happens...
Just pretend it all never happened
♬(Humming “Hi Ho”)
♬〜
《Did we meet somewhere? 》
(Mayumi) Hello, thank you
Ah (Mayumi) Huh?
I forgot to buy snacks for Peter (Mayumi) Huh?
Sorry, Piotr, just let us eat something delicious.
I'll definitely buy it tomorrow.
Piotr with snack
Look, Pyotr, it's okay if you write it properly.
I'll definitely buy it tomorrow, Peter.
What do you usually do? (Kento) Eh, I'm giving it to the teacher.
Are you giving it to your teacher? It's no good if you don't eat it yourself
Please eat properly (Kento) It's okay.
You can't just eat what you like.
(Kento) Okay, thank you.
The teacher will also be full of cucumbers.
If that's the case, you'll be in trouble, right?
good morning
(Tsumura) Ah... Good morning.
I moved to this area yesterday, so I took a walk around here.
Ah... Is that so? Thank you.
This is Tsumura.This is Ninomiya.Here, say hello to Kento.
Hello
Ah... I'm sorry.
Sorry, excuse me
Yes, please be careful when you go.
(Kento) I'll go. Hurry. Come.
Yay! See you then
Hehehe
♬〜
Peter... what's wrong?
No, I dreamed that Peter died... Huh?
Ah... I'm glad you're alive
Don't say anything sinister... I'm sorry.
(Aina) Do you want to go? (Rie) I want to go
(Aina) Let's go Good morning.
(Aina) Ah, good morning, Igawa-san, Igawa-san, this.
It's a pineapple cake, thank you
Huh? Where did you go? It's Taiwan
I was suddenly told that if I didn't use my paid leave, it would be gone.
I've had a lot of rest
That's right
What's wrong? You look pale
Ah... I had a rather unpleasant dream.
What kind of dream is it?
My pet bird is dying...
Huh, sparrow died the other day...
(Sound of tapping on desk) Yes! What is a bad dream?
He's sweaty and sweaty.
(Aina) Tada-san has dreams like that too.
That's surprising! I'll see.
Being chased or something
(Aina) Ah, quite a lot of people watch it.
(Tada) Big thumb
(Aina) It was very rare (Tada) Not really.
(Rie) Motomura-san is for 3 days.
Is 3 pairs of pants and 15 pads okay?
Ah, I lost my putts the last two days.
This time I would like 20 pieces, please.Yes.
(Rie) What happened?
Ah... What about Mr. Tsukamoto?
《Igawa-kun? Hehehehe》
(Rie) Huh? Haven't you heard? Mr. Tsukamoto has moved.
Huh? It looks like your family is moving.
to nearby facilities
Huh? Huh? Is that so? That's right
♬〜
(unlock sound)
I'm home
Kya!
♬〜
Sorry to disturb you.
I ran into Kento-kun just as he was coming back.
While we were talking, I saw a photo of my father.
He's going to show me a lot of things.
♬〜
Was that so?
Sorry
Oh no, not at all
Then I...
♬〜
(sound of breathing)
Kento: You can't force it, right?
That person said that, right?
Show me your dad's photo
♬〜
From now on, don't give it to people you don't know much about, okay?
I understand, I'm sorry
Shall we clean up?
Yeah yeah
yes
Kento: This is the place I used to go with my dad.
Do you remember?
Kento: It looked like a lot of fun.
I don't remember at all
♬〜
Uncle Osamu told me
Even if I can't remember the memories
It's stored away somewhere in your head.
Is that so? Yeah
Dad loved Kento
Ah, shall we go here next Saturday?
Yeah! Yeah
Hehehehe
(Mitsuru/Takako) Hello, thank you.
(Mitsuru) Good work (Takako) What did you buy?
(Ms.) I don't want to hear things like that.
why? Did you buy something you can't tell?
Oh, no, no, that's not it, it's a pet snack.
What do you mean "what"?
Is normal not good? Or rather, what is normal?
So-so, so-so
Well, that's it for me (Takako)
Hello, I'm sorry, hehehehe
(Mayumi)《Peter...》
Ah...
ah…
Are you okay? Ah, sorry
I have a slight headache... Should I call an ambulance?
Oh, it's really okay...
♬〜
Welcome back
what happened? Ah, it's okay.
♬〜
(Mayumi) Ma-kun?
Are you okay?
I have a headache. I'll bring some medicine right away.
♬〜
(Kousaka) Thank you for waiting.
There's something delicious I discovered recently.
I'm a little late, but let's celebrate my release from prison.
thank you
Did something happen?
About Masaki Igawa
I told you not to get involved anymore.
Masaki Igawa has lost his memory of the past few days.
Huh?
A lot of strange things are happening
It's not just Masaki Igawa, there's something about that city itself...
(Kousaka) Why are you so obsessed?
Masaki Igawa looks like Yusuke Ninomiya
Is it that important?
I understand how you feel
But I want you to start a new life
♬〜
when you kill someone
I don't have that
♬〜
I'll make sure not to cause any trouble to Kosaka-san.
《Everyone please join hands》
(Ninomiya)《Itadakimasu》 (Kento Yuri)《Itadakimasu》
♬〜
(Mayumi) Did you have another bad dream?
Sorry, wake me up
Are you okay?
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
I see.
That would be great...
♬〜
(coughing)
(Mayumi) Are you okay? ambulance…
It's okay (Mayumi) It's not okay, right?
No matter how you look at it, it's a hospital...
No... the cucumber might have gone bad.
Huh?
Hey look
There's so many over there!
Is it delicious to eat a lot? (Sage) Yeah
(Child) Yeah, it's delicious. Would you like to exchange it?
(Child) Why not? That's fine
So, Mom, do you want to change it? (Female) Yeah, okay.
Can I buy you some ice cream? Huh? What about potatoes?
Yeah
Because it's special, right?
Well then, yay!
Hehe, be careful
⚟♬“Hi Ho”
♬〜
♬(Sage)《Let's go home, let's go home, I'm hungry》
"what? That》《``Hi Ho!'' 》
《Hahahaha》 《Wow, that’s amazing》
《Did you come up with the lyrics yourself? " "Yeah! 》
《Oh, let's sing, daddy too》 《What? 》
♬《Let's go home Let's go home What's for food? 》
《What? 》
♬《Today is cooked rice》
《Oh!》 《Yay, Seino...》
♬(3 people)《Let's go home, let's go home, I'm hungry》
♬《Let's go home, let's go home, let's go home》
♬《Let's go home, let's go home》
♬《Let's go home, let's go home, I'm hungry》
♬(“Hi Ho” whistle)
Mr. Igawa!
Ah...
That song...
Why are you playing that song now?
(Mayumi) Ma-kun?
Sorry to keep you waiting. Yeah.
acquaintance?
no…
(Sage) Mom!
♬〜
Let's go!
(Mayumi) Ma-kun
♬〜
Hey, that person from earlier...
I felt like I knew someone I didn't know, but
No, really, you don't have to hide it.
Like someone you used to date? No, it's not true.
♬〜
Again...
Huh?
Memories I don't know are floating in my head
What do you mean?
I don't know
♬〜
Someone who looks like my dad has gone somewhere.
Hey
Let's go home, I'm sorry, it was your favorite place.
I thought it would be a change of pace
Thank you, it's okay, let's go.
♬〜
《Oh, I just kicked it》 《Really? 》
《Yes, ah, I kicked it again》 《What? 》
《Here and here》
《Is this what you mean? 》《Hehehehe》
《So maybe I'll be a dancer in the future》 《Hehehe, try it again》
(Ninomiya)《Like this? 》《Hehehe, like this? 》
♬〜
(Ninomiya)《(Hard breathing)》
(sigh)
(sound of glass breaking)
♬〜
Huh!
(Mayumi) Ma-kun? Are you okay?
Ah, I better not come. I'm sorry, I broke your cup.
Ah, I'll bring the broom, thank you.
♬〜
(Kento) I'm coming, you're welcome.
(chime)
Welcome back, I forgot...
I have a story
I'm Yusuke Ninomiya's friend from college.
Huh?
Wait, so suddenly...
Why didn't you say that first?
I didn't want to confuse you.
what do you mean?
Why do I get confused when I hear that?
it is…
I didn't see her at my husband's funeral.
There was something that I couldn't ask you about at that time.
The story is about Yusuke Ninomiya.
What is it?
Masaki Igawa, do you know?
With Masaki Igawa
We compared Yusuke Ninomiya's DNA.
The DNA of these two people is...
matched
Masaki Igawa and Yusuke Ninomiya are the same person
♬〜
Well then, I'll go. Welcome.
It can't be like that...
I saw my husband's body
Did you see the face? yes
The damage was severe, but...
♬〜
Impossible...
Like that...
♬〜
“When I woke up, no one remembered me.”
``Then who am I?'' 》
♬(3 people)《Let's go home, let's go home, I'm hungry》
♬《(“Hi Ho” whistle)》
Is Mr. Igawa really your husband?
yes
Then why are you forgetting me and Kento?
We met and talked the other day
I also ate food here...
I forgot everything
What's wrong with my husband?
I'll find out
So please don't do anything and be as usual.
♬〜
As expected, the Kosaka group is rough with people.
(Kousaka) What did you ask me to do? It's a DNA match. From Tsujimoto.
That too in a hurry
Yes (Hatanaka) Next, if you are in a hurry,
The back of the sleeve? Please
♬〜
good morning
(Rie) Well, let's go home and sleep today.
(Tada) Miyazaki-san
You left some food behind, right? That's no good.
I need to get more excited (Aina) Mr. Taguchi I feel good.
Let's go slowly, slowly
(Rie) The weather is nice today, so it feels good to take a walk.
♬〜
you are my husband
I was with Mayumi the whole time, no, she was with us.
That's Ninomiya. I understand (Kousaka) It's similar to someone else's, right?
That guy really thinks he's Masaki Igawa.
How can I get my memory back?
(Takagishi) Do you know anything about Mayumi Igawa?
(Rie) If I remember unnecessary things...
Should I delete it again?
Let's live together somewhere else
(Takagishi) I understand the true identity of Mayumi Igawa.
(Kousaka) I have a feeling that something is wrong.